stylesatlife.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy | Styles At Life

**Privacy Policy**

At Stylesatlife.com, we believe in keeping our customers and clients alike, safe, secure and happy at all times. This is why we are trusted on all counts, since trust brings in the much needed happiness. Your privacy and safety online is of utmost importance to us, and hence, we have brought about important clauses in this Privacy Policy which would let you know more about how we deal with information that we collect through our website, [stylesatlife.com](http://stylesatlife.com/)

We would ask you to please read on and be well-informed for the same, especially before you use any of the features, products and services, [stylesatlife.com](http://stylesatlife.com/) has to offer.

**Disclaimer:** By using [stylesatlife.com](http://stylesatlife.com/), its features and services, customers and clients are bound by the clauses entailed in our Privacy Policy. Should you wish to disagree or think otherwise, we request you not to use our website and the features or services it provides.

**Information gathering**

Information gathered when clients register on [stylesatlife.com](http://stylesatlife.com/), its features and services would include customer’s personal details such as

  1. full name
  2. email address
  3. location
  4. age
  5. date of birth
  6. gender
  7. physical address
  8. interests

We also collect non-identifiable information, such as;

  1. Internet protocol address
  2. Browser type
  3. Operating system in use
  4. Domain name of the ISP used
  5. Visited web pages
  6. Visited content
  7. Visited advertisements

**How we collect information**

Through advanced and specialised technology, our team gathers and collects information. Some of the methods we use are;

  * Cookies: They dont have personal information of a client, but if the client shares it online, it would be stored
  * Web beacons: There are electronic images on our site known as web beacons, which allows us to keep a count on the number of visits we have every hour, web related statistics, content popularity and more. Web beacon doesn’t infringe into your personal details or space.
  * IP Addresses: The IP address is collected which identifies which computer is connected online to us and from where. It only helps diagnose server problems, site administration and traffic measurement towards our site.

**How we use collected information**

  * Transaction and processing of requests from you to us
  * Communicate with you in various forms and vice-versa
  * Site improvement, feedback, suggestions, queries, updates, services and features
  * Legal terms enforcement for website use and applicable decree
  * Protection of the site and it’s team backend, including customers safety and security
  * Website analysis
  * Improvisation on site usage, content and design, features and services, deliverables etc

**When do we share information?**

  * With sister concerns that helps as data storage providers
  * Communication channels
  * Transaction processing done through merchant accounts through our site
  * Direct marketing from sister concern sites
  * To announce names of winners
  * Law enforcement authorities
  * If the customer has allowed us to specifically do so
  * When a merger, sale, transfer or divestiture happens
  * Anyone below the legal age of 13, information is not collected from knowingly

**Information is safe and respected**

  1. High security measures in place to ensure the customers confidentiality and security at all times. Should you have someone less than 13 years of age and registered on our site, do let us know for instant removal of the same. Do remember, transacting, communicating and transmitting information on our website or anywhere online is not fool proof hundred percent, hence please decide for yourself what you would like to share and what you dont want to, it shall be respected by us.
  2. With regard to sharing information with third party holders, only sites that resonate with the features and services such as ours would be allowed “links” on our page. [stylesatlife.com](http://stylesatlife.com/) strictly opposes an endorsement of any third party product or service, and we do not take it on us for the information clients share with them, when clicking their links or accessing the third party sites online. We ask you to please review the privacy policy, guidelines and reviews of the third party’s website before engaging with them on any level.

**Amendments**

The Privacy Policy as given can be changed, altered, revised in part or completely, as and when deemed fit by the owners and the team of [stylesatlife.com](http://stylesatlife.com/). The effect would be immediate and every customer would be notified through various communication channels, as registered with us.

For further queries, contact us at [info@stylesatlife.com](mailto:info@stylesatlife.com) , [prahalya@stylesatlife.com](mailto:prahalya@stylesatlife.com) .
